I think I'll go see a movie.
What about you, Kugisaki?
It's still early. I'll go shopping or something.
You all have so much energy.
I'm going home, then.
Take care.
Finally done.
I'm going to the movies. What about you?
What are you seeing?
Human Earthworm 4.
Who'd ever go see that?
I haven't even seen 1, 2, or 3.
I think you'd be fine jumping in on 4.
This time, the mad scientist
from the first one,
Dr. Richter, is making his
long-awaited reappearance!
Stop! Let me go!
And the hybrid human-earthworm fusion
born from the doctor's experiments
is going to give rise to an
enhanced Human Earthworm!
What the hell? That's so gross.
The poor Human Earthworm, who barely
escaped from Dr. Richter with its life,
finally wanders into a campground
where a group of college students are,
and that's when the story really kicks off.
So, one of the people in that group is a kind
woman who's an animal rights proponent,
and the Human Earthworm
falls in love with her.
I'm no longer human.
You're more human than anyone else.
It's a monster! Kill it!
Kevin, stop!
If we kill him, then we're the monsters!
Papa.
Papa?
Are you okay?
What's wrong?
Human Earthworm 4
So the theme is actually love!
I don't want see some wormo man,
regardless of the theme.
It's "Human Earthworm."
It doesn't matter.
I'm going shopping, okay?
Want to come with?
I just said I'm going to the movies.
Okay. Later, then.
Special-grade is a rank reserved for
those sorcerers who are exceptional.
In my opinion, first-grade is
the true rank for the sorcerers
who will lead other sorcerers
and jujutsu society.
They must stand above comparison to semi-first-
grades in terms of peril, secrecy, and salary.
Now, with that in mind,
what did you just say?
Maki Zen'in, Panda...
...Megumi Fushiguro, Nobara Kugisaki,
and my brother, Yuji Itadori.
On my name as Aoi Todo...
And on my name as Mei Mei...
I recommend those five
for first-grade sorcerer.
Those who are recommended
by at least two first-grades
must carry out missions under
an active first-grade,
or first-grade equivalent sorcerer.
Then, if they are deemed fit,
they will be promoted to semi-first-grade
and proceed to be assigned
first-grade missions on their own.
Following the results of those missions,
they either will or won't officially
become first-grade sorcerers.
My brother will certainly accept
the recommendation.
With Sukuna still uncooperative,
he'll need to go on more dangerous missions
to raise his chances of finding more fingers.
You understand what
that means, right, Ms. Mei?
What that means?
That's everything, Mr. Todo.
A bright future...
It means a bright future
where Aoi Todo and Yuji Itadori
face missions together lies ahead of us!
No...
You don't have to say it.
There's no guarantee I'll be the first-grade
sorcerer assigned to accompany him.
That's what you wanted to say, right?
But I'm certain of this!
It's as certain as apples
falling from a tree!
The two of us are drawn together!
Yes, it truly is destiny!
No, I mean...
The sorcerers who recommended him
can't be assigned to accompany him.
Since we're the two that
recommended Itadori-kun,
someone else will have to accompany him.
Thanks for today.
I'll be leaving now, Mr. Todo.
Um, excuse me.
You were with Itadori-kun earlier, right?
Huh?
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Shibuya Incident
Welcome!
This is what I looked like at our
middle school graduation ceremony.
Huh?! Seriously?! That was only six months ago!
What happened to you?!
Well, I've grown about
15 centimeters since then.
That combined with the stress of moving
to Tokyo and changing environments...
Wow...
You're a real Kuroko Sato.
That's Itadori.
On graduation day, I worked up the
courage to ask for a photo with him.
I actually wanted to ask
for his phone number,
but it was already decided
that we would be moving to Tokyo...
So when I saw Itadori-kun earlier,
I thought maybe with
how I look now, I might...
Wait... Yuko, you mean...
It's like that, right?
Yes! It's like that!
Hey, Ijichi-san.
Is Fushiguro still riding with you?
I sent you the URL for the restaurant I'm at.
Could you turn around and bring him here?
Thanks! See ya soon!
Someone who knows Itadori well
is on his way here now.
Um...
We'll talk to him about it first.
If you're also interested in Itadori-kun...
No.
Even if hell froze over
and danced the lambada...
No.
My chest just felt weird.
Did my heart skip a beat?
Did my heart
skip a beat?
Yo, what's the big idea?
Hey, Fushiguro!
Does Itadori have a girlfriend?
Huh?
This is Yuko Ozawa.
She's actually blah, blah, blah.
So it's like that?!
Yeah, it's like that!
He definitely doesn't have a girlfriend.
Your basis for that?
When he suddenly had to transfer to Tokyo,
he didn't seem particularly upset about it.
He also has a pinup
poster hanging in his room.
Anyone with a girlfriend wouldn't have
something like that hanging up, right?
Because she'd hate it.
Are you the type to drink coffee black only
when women are around so you can show off?
Stop that.
You called me out here
to ask me about this, right?
And I always drink it black.
Um, by the way, do you know what his type is?
He mentioned he likes tall girls.
You have a shot!
I'll summon Itadori!
You're okay with that, right, Yuko?!
Yes!
Yuji Itadori
Hey.
FAMILY Restaurant
Come.
Why?
Got it.
That was curt.
Was it?
Hey, Fushiguro's here, too!
That was fast!
Oh, crap.
What's that?
I didn't tell Itadori about Yuko!
Finding a money exchange was a pain,
so I traded in for prizes instead.
He definitely won't recognize her
after she changed so much!
Who are you?
That's the number one line you don't want to
hear when reuniting with the one you adore!
Itadori!
This girl is—
Wait...
You're Ozawa. What are you doing here?
What a coincidence.
Okay, so which girl in our
class do you like, Itadori?
None of them, really.
But if you had to pick!
Huh?
If I had to pick, then... Ozawa.
What?!
No way, man! She's fat!
Is she?
But the way she eats and her handwriting
and stuff are super nice.
I mean, fish is hard to eat, you know?
I thought you said you liked
tall girls with big butts?
That's its own thing!
It's easy for girls to get fat.
I started off fat...
But even I don't have any interest in
choosing someone who won't choose me.
Itadori-kun saw a side of me I wasn't aware of.
I hated all the boys other than Itadori-kun.
But...
"Maybe with how I look now, I might..."
I'm living by the same
standards as the people I hate.
Later.
See you tomorrow.
See you later.
Was that really okay?
They could have at least exchanged numbers.
I exchanged with her. It should be fine.
More importantly, Fushiguro,
I've finally realized my own feelings.
Huh?
The thought that Itadori
might land a girlfriend
before I get a boyfriend pisses me off.
That so?
Sorry for the wait.
Walk behind me.
Huh? Say what? What are you talking about?
Here.
Oh! Thanks!
Huh? Huh? What's this?
Just while you're at it.
While I'm at it?
You'd feel bad making
a lady carry them, right?
Sure.
Oh, crap! The movie's starting!
Hey, let's go!
Huh?! Hold up!
Come on, come on, come on!
Don't take mine with you!
There's no way I'm watching some wormo man!
You want some popcorn, too, Fushiguro?
You like caramel flavor, right?
Don't just advance the conversation
assuming we're gonna see wormo man.
I told you all, it's Human Earthworm 4!
Episode 30
It's Like That
Impossible!
Working with a curse user is
one thing, but cursed spirits?!
Yet, lately, cursed spirits of that level
have been popping up everywhere.
The person in question may think they're
only working with curse users, though.
I want to leave the investigation
of Kyoto up to you, Utahime.
This way.
You've heard from Gojo about
the person leaking intel, right?
Yes.
There's probably two or more people
in contact with the curse users.
One would be a higher-up,
well above the principal.
I won't be able to do
anything about that one.
The other would be someone passing
the information up to that higher-up.
That one is our current target.
They're only a suspect at this point,
so we'll capture and interrogate them.
So, who from Kyoto is it?
Oh?!
That's why you asked those
of us from Tokyo, right?
Kugisaki, you're incredible.
The mole is...
Mechamaru!
Oh, there you are.
Today's the last day
to turn in your notebook.
Mechamaru?
Sorry, Miwa. I'm going to sleep for a bit.
Please take the notebook from my desk.
Sleep? It's still only evening.
Jeez!
Poke Poke Poke
He really did go to sleep.
I wonder where the real
Mechamaru actually is.
Mechamaru's real body,
Kokichi Muta, is in the basement here.
Now, it's not like he's suspicious.
It's more that everyone else wasn't.
So the process of elimination
leaves us with him.
Mechamaru's technique
is puppet manipulation.
Thanks to his Heavenly Pact,
the range he can manipulate puppets
in extends throughout all of Japan.
If he had unregistered puppets,
he could do the work of a
mole as much as he wanted.
Really?
That guy stood out a lot to me.
Even if the puppet was
the size of a fly or a mosquito?
I see.
So those are options, too, huh?
We're here.
They've arrived?
Uh...
He got us.
But on the other hand...
Now we're certain it's Mechamaru.
You're late.
I thought you forgot about me.
We wouldn't make a blunder like that.
You're personally familiar with the
terrifying nature of a pact, right?
He always smells moldy. I hate it.
And he's an enemy. Let's just kill him quick.
You can't do that yet, Mahito.
He agreed to cooperate with us
and provide information.
In exchange, we agreed to use your
Idle Transfiguration to fix his body.
That's the pact we all forged, remember?
Killing him comes after fixing him.
I wanted him to do some work
for us in Shibuya, too,
so that's a shame.
"We won't lay a hand on the people
from the Kyoto school."
You're the ones who broke our pact first.
Hanami's the one who did that.
You shouldn't lash out at the wrong people.
I have no intention of
arguing with cursed spirits.
Hurry up and fix me, scumbag.
Maybe I'll get carried away
and turn him into a caterpillar.
Mahito.
Pacts forged with others are very different
from pacts placed upon oneself.
The first aspect of that is the
uncertain nature of the penalty.
If you break a pact with yourself,
whatever you gained,
the improvement to your own ability is lost,
but this time, you can't break it.
If you break this pact,
then we have no idea when or
what kind of disaster will befall us.
Yeah, yeah.
You're lower than a scumbag, so be grateful.
Idle Transfiguration.
No fun at all.
Celebrate a bit more.
I'll do that after I'm finished here.
I suppose that's fair.
All right, shall we get started?
Want my help?
Don't you dare. He's my toy.
He escaped?
Well, it's not like we need to kill him.
How boring.
I wanted to have a match,
not go hunting, you know.
That's more like it!
Ultimate Mechamaru, Mode: Absolute
“Armored Puppet Ultimate Mechamaru Prototype 0”
So you've been making
something like this in secret?
Guess you weren't a shut-in just for show.
He's inside it, right?
He wouldn't want me to touch him, after all.
The cockpit...
The seat of his soul...
is the head!
Expansion rate normal.
Perception feedback severed.
Tsk. They lowered a veil.
Must be Geto.
It's not just attempting to trap me inside.
It's cutting off signal, too.
This won't be as easy as
it was for Satoru Gojo.
That's right. My victory
condition is Satoru Gojo.
I have to use any means necessary
to get in contact with Satoru Gojo,
and tell him about the Shibuya plot.
Then I'll have him protect me.
But even if I want to focus on Geto,
the one who lowered this veil,
Mahito, is too dangerous to ignore.
I'll have to exorcise him first.
Go ahead, don't mind me.
I'm still at a disadvantage.
But I have a chance to win.
I've seen it all.
I have all the time I was bound. All the
cursed energy I gained from that time.
I won't hold anything back.
17 years 1 month 29 days
16 Years
Charge, one year!
Burn him, Mechamaru!
Ultra Cannon!
I decided I'd never tell anyone about
the things I truly want to keep secret
after I wrote what type of
boy I like in my profile book
back in grade school
and had everyone find out!
Next time, "Evening Festival"!
Next Episode
Evening Festival
What did you write?
Mittermeyer.
He does seem like he'd be fast.